All right!
Yes!
Someone needs to fill in for Yoshitsune.
Akutsu, you're playing forward.
Great!
The center-back's playing as a forward now?
He's not freakin' Tulio!
Being promoted doesn't necessarily mean you're ready for a match.
If you're not getting much game time on the A-team,
I'll try to field you in the B-team games,
so make sure you're leaving those times available.
Feels like we're not really on the team, just in limbo.
If they want me to earn my place, then so be it.
Give me one month.
I'll be the best starter they've ever seen.
Hmm. Oh, well. I guess I can't expect too much.
I am surprised Ashito wasn't promoted, though.
We won both games thanks to him, so I figured he'd be a lock.
Yeah.
Hmm.
I thought they'd be moving him up despite his problem areas.
I mean, we all have them.
It's Fukuda, right?
He's known to make bold choices when it comes to his players.
Hey. Where is he?
Uh-huh.
Huh.
Aisaku Otomo, Soichiro Tachibana, Ashito Aoi.
Those are my picks for this year's tryouts.
They're the only ones worth remembering.
Aoi won't cut it.
No amount of practice will get him where we need him.
He's never gonna have what it takes to play on Aspirion's front line.
I'm gonna turn him into a defender.
What you think?
Wait, you mean as a fullback?
That's right. It makes sense to me.
No way. He won't want to change his position.
We can't just force him to.
I need your support. Trust me.
I'll be the one to tell him when the time's right.
Whoa. Hold on. Does Ashito know about this yet?
They're trying to make him a defender?
The dude self-destructs if he's not allowed to score.
Later. I'm going for a jog.
What?
Yeah, I'm out.
We need to find him.
Oh, okay. I get it.
The idiot doesn't have a cell phone, does he?
Wait for me!
Um, you know, it is almost curfew.
So I guess I should really get going, too.
Today's the enrollment ceremony.
Is this a joke?
You're fielding Aoi as a forward?
Just when are you planning to tell him about the Switch?
It's just for a couple of games. Not that big a deal.
What exactly is the point of that?
Before we can discuss his position, he needs to master the basics.
Let him play what he knows.
His skills have got to improve first.
I've said this before.
He's not going to accept it.
You can't make him do anything he doesn't want.
Listen. He's by the window now.
I want you to motivate him.
Say he don't think he'll cut it as a forward loud enough for him to hear.
His strength lies in his defiance.
I promise this is the best thing we can do for him.
But I need you to be the bad guy.
I'm sorry.
Please.
Fukuda.
Up to now, everything's turned out the way you said it would.
Things always happen the way you predict they will.
It's an unspoken rule.
We all know it.
I can't believe we killed it.
That means I really am good enough, Nozomi.
It's true.
No one would have guessed this was your debut.
Give me three years.
I'll be a key player by then.
I'll make a name for myself out here and then head off to Europe.
It's going to happen.
Just watch me.
You're a piece of work, Fukuda.
This plan?
Ashito Aoi playing fullback?
If by some miracle he agrees to it, that'll open up unlimited possibilities for both of you.
However, I can't allow you to bulldoze your way through this time.
Was this really the best way to go about it?
Was it the appropriate moment?
Or did you finally get it wrong?
We'll see.
I just got a strange text from Yuma.
He said Aoi hasn't been back to the dorm at all.
Have you heard from him, Hana?
Do you have any idea where he might be?
Look at me.
There's no life in your eyes.
Have you eaten yet?
All clear.
Perfect, right?
Place is completely vacant.
No one from the academy is using it today.
I knew they wouldn't be because I used to work here.
You can sit wherever.
I'm going to cook for you.
Boom, now what?
Hana.
Hmm?
You showed up like you knew where I would be.
But how could you?
Henri told me what happened earlier, and then I just sort of filled in the gaps.
Match had finished a while ago, but you weren't at the dorm.
Oh, you were still on your kit, so in a crowd, you'd be spotted and someone would let the team know right away.
Which meant you couldn't be downtown or at the train station.
I may not know much about soccer, but even I could figure out this would be tough on you.
I knew you would be taking it hard and that you'd want to run, maybe even as far as home to Ehime.
In order to get there, you'd have to go to a bus stop first.
Still, I didn't really think I'd find you, but I sure did.
First try.
Like, there, you were.
I think I completely blacked out until you showed up.
Even sitting at this table feels like we're in a dream.
Here's what I do know.
Your brother's a jerk.
He's a monster.
I'm sure it feels that way, but he has a reason for everything.
Regardless, I don't know what it means to change positions, but I know being the one to score was truly important to you.
I'm sorry.
So what will you do?
Are you gonna quit?
I won't quit.
Couldn't afford to anyway.
I'm stuck here.
I'll zone out a bit longer, then I'll head back.
I've got to.
I'm sorry, Hana.
It all looks good.
But the last thing on my mind is eating.
I'm a defender.
Defender?
How?
What's going on?
Hello?
Hana, it's late.
Why are you calling at this hour?
Are you there?
Is everything okay?
Hello?
Ashito.
Ashito, is that you?
It is, right?
Did something happen?
Don't get too worked up, okay?
If it's not panning out, then just come home.
I promise, it's not a big deal.
Nothing's changed.
I'm fine.
Everything's great.
I promise.
Please don't worry.
Night.
I know it's a lot of pressure and probably really overwhelming, but don't tell yourself
you only have one option.
Don't sit there with that look in your eyes and say you can't afford to quit.
Like I said, I don't know much about this sport, so I don't know what you're going through.
But I'm hoping you'll take a step back and see it's just soccer, for goodness sake.
I heard your mom on the phone.
She was being supportive.
She's there, whatever you decide.
I'm hungry now.
Can I?
Of course.
Yes.
Hey, Akutsu.
I heard a bunch of chaos in the lobby.
Did something happen?
Oh, Kuromayashi?
What are you doing here?
Since when do you dwell amongst the lowly?
Aren't you on the bench for J1's game tomorrow?
There was someone here I was hoping to chat with before the match.
You've seen Ashito Aoi?
Anyway, it's not that important.
I just can't find him.
The chaos you heard in the lobby before was about him.
He hasn't returned to the dorm yet.
How come?
He was useless as a forward, so he got switched to a defender.
Then he stormed off, pouting like a loser.
I hope that dude quits and doesn't come back.
But why would he quit over something like that, huh?
He should totally play fullback on the line.
It's clear if you watch him.
He wouldn't have gotten in otherwise.
You knew that, right?
Hey, you know, you should coach him on how to defend.
I mean, that would make the most sense, don't you think?
Shut up!
Come on, we used to talk about this a lot.
About how we needed a fullback to complete Fukuda's big picture.
Ashito!
Where the heck have you been?
We looked everywhere for you.
Where'd you go?
You did?
Oh, I'm sorry, man.
Mm-hmm.
So what the crap?
Curfew.
I broke it.
Gotta go apologize to the dorm, Mom.
Ashito.
Hmm.
You gotta be kidding me right now.
You're completely useless as a forward,
so we're supposed to train you as a defender instead?
Do you know how big of a pain in the ass
that's gonna be for the rest of us defenders?
Did that hit a nerve?
You know, maybe soccer's not for you.
Are you ready to give up?
Hmm.
I am not giving up.
But I don't know how to defend.
So I'm going to need your help.
Please teach me everything you know.
Huh?
Thank you for this, Hana.
I don't want to be a defender.
I really don't.
But there's no other way.
I don't want to be a defender.
Hmm?
Hmm.
He seems to have a lot going on.
I can try him another time.
I'm curious about this meal plan I found last week.
I wonder who made it for him.
The more I look at it, the better it seems.
What happened to your face, bro?
The doorm mother sent me flying.
She is seriously scary when you piss her off.
Well, you ready?
Maybe.
For what?
We're going to go over the basics of being a defender.
I hope you didn't think anyone else was going to teach you.
Mind if I join you, too?
I figure I owe you one.
Uh, hey, Asuri.
You owe me?
You mean because of that fight?
I'm a cut above, so I'm moving up to the A-team.
As a parting gift,
I thought I'd teach you a little bit about being a defender.
Look, I'm not Kodura or Takashima,
so I can be here, right?
Um, hello?
Thank you, both of you.
I would love your help!
So, you're a defender now.
That's going to change up the game a lot for you.
It won't be easy.
In fact, one thing in particular
I know you'll struggle with.
Uh-huh.
Well, am I right?
The shuffle.
I suggest you figure out the full meaning of that word.
If you can't do that,
then you won't be playing a single game.
Feel me?
Uh...
So, about the shuffle.
Let me see.
I guess we can say we start off with four defenders.
Then one of the fullbacks starts heading upfield.
Once they leave,
that's going to create a big old space right here.
It's up to you to fill that space quickly.
So, how would you do that?
Look at your other defenders.
You'll see all three of them start shuffling sideways.
They're keeping it tight in the center.
Moving over to plug a huge gap like that
is what we call the shuffle.
Got it?
Makes it harder to reach the goal.
Hey!
I was going to say that!
No.
Oh, this is ridiculous.
Even I can tell you that much?
Come on!
Fukuda's not here.
We'll train as a group first,
then we can play a quick mini-game
and call it for the day.
A and B teams will split into two groups,
nine each.
Then do 20-minute nine-on-nines.
The goal for this exercise
is to make sure each member of your team
has a clear idea of their position and its role.
Therefore, I suggest you refrain
from getting overly physical.
All right.
Take a second to check the lineups
and confirm your positions.
So,
old man Fukuda dipped out.
It's fine.
Actually, I'm glad he's not here.
I don't want to see him.
I'll do it.
I'll give this a try.
Looks like Asari and Kuda
are having a tough time.
Man,
that A-team's not messing around.
Am I right, Ashito?
Oh,
come on, hurry it up.
Unless you're not wanting to play today.
I do!
How are you feeling?
Not too bad.
That's good to hear.
Just do your best.
Seriously?
A fullback stands this far away from everything?
It's a totally different view from a forwards.
It's like a whole new perspective.
I can see everyone from here.
My team,
their team.
I can keep an eye on every player as a fullback.
It's an advantage.
It's good you're here.
Listen,
just do your best.
I control the line.
All eyes on me.
Both Togashi and I
were full attack-minded.
If you want advice on defending,
then Takashima is your best bet.
Aspirion's a major attacking team now,
but he's been a defender since he was a kid.
The attack against Sekio worked
because we knew Takashima had our backs.
Um, actually,
I was wondering if there was anything
I should do specifically.
The shuffle.
Since that's the whole point of being a fullback.
If you can manage to get that down,
then I don't care if you go and join the attack
or stay out here.
I've made up my mind.
I'm ready to crush this.
Let's go!
Hmm.
Next time on Awashi, where I ought to be.